[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What film company released the film Shrek the Third?", "correct_answer": "Dreamworks", "incorrect_answers": ["Disney", "Universal", "New Line"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where would you find the highest tides on Earth?", "correct_answer": "Bay of Fundy", "incorrect_answers": ["Hawaii", "Cape of Good Hope", "Cape Horn"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The volume of the Earths moon is the same as the volume of the Pacific and Indian Oceans combined.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Kurt Wagner is the alter ego of which character?", "correct_answer": "Nightcrawler", "incorrect_answers": ["Spawn", "Mockingbird", "Wonder Woman"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What kind of cells carry oxygen around your body?", "correct_answer": "red blood cells", "incorrect_answers": ["fat cells", "oxygen cells", "blue cells"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who were the legendary founders of  the city of Rome?", "correct_answer": "Romulus and Remus", "incorrect_answers": ["Castor and Pollux", "Troilus and Cressida", "Damon and Pythias"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this cult horror flick, directed by Sam Raimy, the dead start to emerge after a tape recording of demonic incantations from The Book of The Dead are played.", "correct_answer": "The Evil Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ancient Book", "Necronomicon", "Evil Zombies"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of conic section would this mathematical equation produce: (x^2)/4+(y^2)/9=81?", "correct_answer": "Ellipse", "incorrect_answers": ["Line", "Circle", "Ray"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not among the systems of the human body that vitamins of the B group mainly benefit?", "correct_answer": "Respiratory", "incorrect_answers": ["Cardio-vascular", "Immune", "Digestive"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "\u201cThe Exorcist\u201d, rated as the scariest movie of all time, is burlesqued in which part of  \u201cScary Movie\u201d?", "correct_answer": "Scary Movie 2", "incorrect_answers": ["Scary Movie 4", "Scary Movie 3", "Scary Movie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Humans and human descendants hunted dinosaurs for food.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Chinese Crested dog does not require much exercise.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]